Помідори
Огірочки
Баклажан
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
Помідори
Огірочки
Баклажан
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
Помідори
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
Помідори
Огірочки
Баклажан
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
Помідори
Огірочки
Баклажан
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
Помідори
Огірочки
Баклажан
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
Hoshimi Production
Ну що, всі тут?
Are we all here?
Чому ти всіх нас зібрав... перед заняттями?
Why did you have us gather before practice?
Спокійно, просто послухайте.
Be calm and just listen.
Нам відома дата дебюту.
Our debut concert is set!
Га?
What? Huh?
Щось вони не в захваті.
They don't seem too excited.
Дебют...
Debut...
Наш дебют...
Our...
Котоно.
Kotono...
Коли він?
When is it?
nee, yakusoku dayo
kakegae no nai stage wo
Ah ready? We go! Yes!
Please take me out!
Stand up! Without you!
nemurenai yoru to setsunai asa wo
tsunagi tomeru no wa yume nandakara
ushinai kaketa utagoe mo
tomo ni asu ni kimi ni tooi ni hibiku you ni to
toki ni wa mune ga itakute (feeling heart)
sore demo muchuu de
Wake me up! Wake me up!
hikari to kage wo
nee yakusoku dayo
ano basho de kagayaki au koto
kimi to nareba takaku toberu
makenaiyotte waraou
nee yubikiri shiyou
dare hitori furimukanai you ni
zutto tooku wo mite
hashire tsuzuketeiku
Концерт буде на особливій сцені,
The debut concert will be held
on the special stage
на фестивалі Хошімі, одному з найбільших у місті.
at the Hoshimi Festival,
one of Hoshimi City's biggest events.
Це ж там Мана виступала вперше?
That's where Mana had her debut concert.
Так.
Yes.
Я надішлю вам запис пісні і танцю.
I'll give you the debut song recording
and choreography video.
Ми розпочнемо справжні уроки
з професійним тренером в студії.
We'll have you start real lessons with a
professional coach at a studio in the city.
До того впевніться,
що ознайомились з даним матеріалом.
Make sure you familiarize yourself
with the song and dance until then.
Це ж легендарна студія,
де вчилась Мана!
This is the legendary studio
that fostered Miss Mana!
Ну не легендарна,
"Legendary" is an exaggeration.
але ЛізНор і Трінітіейл...
But it's a famous studio where
Вони теж ходять на заняття сюди.
LizNoir and TRINITYAiLE take lessons, too.
До цього моменту були базові тренування,
We were able to focus on
basic training until now,
але відтепер ви будете
зайняті як ніколи раніше.
but from here on out,
you'll be busier than ever.
А ще ми візьмемо участь в програмі "Венера".
And we'll also enter the Venus Program.
Програмі "Венера"...
The Venus Program...
Рейтинг айдолів, базований на розрахунках штучного інтелекту.
An idol ranking system based on AI judgments.
Правильно.
That's right.
Після цього досвід і кар'єра
не маютимуть значення.
Once you make a debut,
experience and career make no difference.
То як, готові?
Do you think you're ready?
Так!
Yes!
Тоді ходімо.
Let's go, everyone.
Я - Номото,
відсьогодні буду вас тренувати.
I'm Nomoto and I'll be
training you all starting today.
Вітаю!
Nice to meet you!
Приємно познайомитись!
Thank you very much!
А ти молодша сестра Мани?
Are you Mana's younger sister?
Так.
Yes.
Зрозуміло.
I see...
Щасти.
Good luck.
Так!
Yes!
Добре, пропоную розпочати з розтяжки.
All right! Now, let's start out
with stretches, shall we?
Що? Прямо вже?
What? Already?
Ну що ж ви?!
Come on!
Не треба втрачати дорогоцінний час.
Don't waste the limited time we have.
Так!
Yes!
Тепер,
Now,
розпочнемо наше інтерв'ю.
let's get started with the interview.
Т-так!
Y-Yes!
Д-дуже Вам такю...Ой!
Th-Thank you vewy mu— Oh!
Дякую.
Very much!
Дівчата, спробуйте не хвилюватись.
Try to relax, everyone.
Мені подобається їх молода енергія.
I love their fresh energy.
Я чула, що Ви ,Саекі Харуко,
найдосвідченіша в групі.
But Miss Haruko Saeki, I heard you are
the experienced one of the group.
Це правда.
Yes.
Я раніше була солісткою.
I used to be a solo artist.
З утворенням групи
я перегортаю нову для себе сторінку.
With the formation of the group,
I'm turning over a new leaf.
з'явилось багато нового,
але я старатимуся
і буду рада підтримці!
I'll be working hard as if I'm a newcomer again,
so I'd love everyone's support!
Красномовно.
So eloquent.
Харуко, це вражаюче!
Haruko, that was impressive!
Дійсно.
Truly.
Хей, як пройшов ваш урок?
Hey! How did your dance lesson go?
Розкажіть про тренера?
What was your coach like?
Сузу тремтить від страху...
Suzu is trembling with fear...
Що? Вона настільки страшна?
What? She's that scary?
Не дивно, що вона навчала Ману.
It is no wonder that she trained Miss Mana.
Немає чого переживати.
There's no need to worry.
Може й сувора,
але в неї дуже ретельний підхід.
She may be strict, but she's very thorough.
Та тренер має бути суворим,
тільки так можна наздогнати Ману.
The coach needs to be strict
so we can catch up to Miss Mana.
А ще...
Plus...
Було весело.
It's a lot of fun.
Га?
Huh?
Тепер я справді бачу наш величезний прогрес.
I get to really see how much we've progressed.
Що таке?
What is it?
А, ні, просто...
Oh, no, um...
Котоно, ми здивувались, коли слово
"весело" прозвучало з твоїх уст.
We all got surprised when the words "it's fun"
came out of your mouth, Kotono.
Та я ж нічого дивного не сказала.
I didn't think I said anything weird...
Мені подобається.
That's great.
Уже чекаю наступних занять.
I can't wait to take our lessons!
А як проходять інтерв'ю?
How did the interview go with you all?
Ну, я дуже нервую і плутаюсь.
I got nervous and fumbled a lot.
Я взагалі не пам'ятаю, що там говорила.
I don't remember... what I said...
Рей, а в тебе?
How about you, Rei?
Все було добре?
Did you speak well?
Не впевнена, що дуже добре,
I'm not sure if I spoke well,
але я вже давала інтерв'ю на змаганнях.
but I've done interviews
at dance competitions, too.
Тут, як і в танцях, потрібна практика.
So, much like dancing, it's all about practice
and getting used to it.
Ми підемо на радіо,
щоб просувати наші концерти,
We'll be appearing on the radio
to promote our concerts,
тому зараз варто потренуватись.
so now would be the time to practice.
Ага.
Yeah.
На радіо...
Radio appearances...
Пані Котоно!
Miss Kotono!
Поділіться з нами ентузіазмом!
Share with us your enthusiasm
about the debut concert!
Га? Ам...
What? Um...
Я не програю.
I won't lose.
Кому саме?
Against who exactly?
Котоно, пізніше попрактикуємось разом?
Kotono, let's practice together later.
Тепер у нас є тренер,
Now we're training with a coach...
Беруть інтерв'ю...
Taking interviews...
Ми дійсно готуємось до нашого виступу!
We're really going to have our debut!
Покажемо клас на концерті, хай там що.
Let's pull off our debut concert
no matter what!
Мг.
Yeah.
Звісно.
Of course.
Цей концер лише наш перший крок.
Making our debut is only the first step.
Ми прагнемо набагато більшого.
What we aim for is beyond that.
Стати найкращими.
To reach the top as idols.
Піднімемось на вершину, як і Мана!
Let's climb to the top, just like Miss Mana!
Знаю! Зробимо те, що ми вчора придумали!
Hey! Let's do our chant
we made up together yesterday!
Чудова ідея!
Good idea!
Зробімо це!
Let's do it!
Що? Зараз?..
What? Now...?
Давай, Котоно!
Come on, Kotono!
Ну добре.
Okay.
Всі готові?
Everyone ready?
Ага.
Yup.
Компанія Хошімі!
Hoshimi Production!
Упе...
Let's!
ред!
Go!
За...
Fight!
палимо!
Yeah!
Гіп-гіп-гіп!
Go, go, go, go!
Ура!
Yeah!
Помідори
Огірочки
Баклажан
TOMATO
CUCUMBER
EGGPLANT
Hoshimi Production
Переможцем сьогоднішнього конкурсу стає...
The victor of today's concert battle is...
Трінітіейл!
...TRINITYAiLE!
Дякуємо вам!
Thank you very much!
Прийміть мої вітання!
Congratulations!
Це був ще один незрівнянний виступ!
You had yet another
unparalleled performance today!
Дуже дякую.
Thank you very much.
Здається, у вас є намір перевершити
рекордну серію перемог Наґасе Мани.
It seems like you've got the momentum to surpass
Miss Mana's record-length winning streak.
Дуже скоро вашій групі не буде рівних,
You're headed to become untouchable,
чи є ідоли, з якими ви хотіли б поборотись?
but is there an idol out there
you'd like to challenge?
Здається, немає.
Not particularly.
Але запевняю, що можу позмагатись з будь-яким ідолом.
But I've got the confidence to beat any idol.
Такою була моя ціль з самого початку.
What I've been aiming for
with this group since the beginning
Стати найкращою.
is to get to the top as idols.
Привіт усім!
Дякую вам за підтримку.
Hey, everyone! Thank you all
for all your support today.
Приходьте до нас ще!
We look forward to your support again!
Руі, ти була такою крутою!
Rui, you were so cool today!
Неперевершена, як завжди.
You come off strong as usual, though.
Я лиш говорю правду.
I'm only speaking the truth.
Ми взлетимо ще вище.
We'll fly even higher.
Правда?
Isn't that right?
Пан Асакура?
Mr. Asakura?
Так.
Yeah.
Я чув про їх дебют.
I've heard about the debut.
І надсилати квіти не планую.
I don't plan on sending any flowers, though.
Невдовзі ми з ними зустрінемось.
We'll be facing each other soon.
Та не будь до нас занадто суворим.
But don't be too hard on us.
Не розчаруй мене.
Don't disappoint me.
Вітаю, президенте!
Hello, President!
Хтось готується до першого виступу?
Is someone going to make their debut?
Компанія Хошімі нарешті.
For the first time in four years
from Hoshimi Production.
Компанія Хошімі?..
Hoshimi Production...
Якщо вони дійсно мають здібності,
If their abilities are real,
колись ви позмагаєтесь також і з ними.
you'll be fighting against them,
too, eventually.
Будьте готові.
Brace yourselves.
І це все?
Is that all you have to say?
Ви ж бачили наш виступ, правда?
You watched our performance, didn't you?
Ми можливо поб'ємо рекорд Мани...
We might break Mana Nagase's
undefeated record—
То й що?
So what?
Поки ви зайняті дурницями,
You won't be able to catch up
to Mana Nagase
наздогнати її не зможете.
when you're preoccupied with stupid things.
Пам'ятайте це.
Remember that.
Руі...
Rui...
Нарешті завтра...
Tomorrow is finally
наш перший концерт!
our debut concert!
Він буде проводитись на сцені фестивалю Хошімі.
It will be held at the special stage
at the Hoshimi Festival.
Чекаємо там вас усіх!
We hope to see you all there!
Бум!
Boom!
Наґісо,
Nagisa?
все добре?
Are you okay?
Вибач.
Sorry about that.
Коли я думаю про завтра,
When I think about tomorrow,
стаю геть не уважна.
my mind goes all over the place.
І що в тебе на думці?
What was on your mind?
Ну, "Чи зможу я гарно заспівати?"
Like, "Will I be able to sing well?"
"Може я десь спіткнуся?"
"Will I mess up the choreography?"
Боюсь, що буду тягнути всіх униз.
I'm scared that I'll hold everyone back.
Дуже хвилююсь.
I'm very nervous.
Чому б нам не заварити смачного чаю?
Why don't we serve the nice black tea today?
І не зняти напругу?
So we can all relax.
Дуже тобі дякую.
Thank you very much.
Нічний чеклист
Допомогти готувати вечерю
Повечеряти
Передивитися танець з музикою.
Night Checklist
Help prepare dinner
Eat dinner
Review choreography and song
Сакі!
Saki!
Ванна готова!
The bath is ready!
Добре.
Okay!
А що це?
What is that?
Я зібрала список справ,
які треба зробити до концерту.
I was putting together a list of things
I need to do before the concert.
Що? Класно!
What? That's amazing!
Зараз особливо хочеться перевірити все.
I want to make sure things go as usual,
especially on important days.
І сказати собі:
So I can tell myself:
"Ти зробила все, що могла і зараз підготовлена."
"You're prepared. You've done
everything you can do right now."
Чісо, Шідзуку.
Chisa, Shizuku.
Не перестарайтесь,
це може погано вплинути.
If you overdo it right now,
it'll affect you tomorrow.
Ще трошки.
Just a little more.
Подивись ще раз, будь ласка.
Please watch us one more time.
Після цього готуйтесь до хорошої розтяжки.
Be ready for a thorough
stretch session after this.
Добре!
Yes!
Завтра...
Tomorrow...
Котоно.
Kotono.
Сакуро.
Sakura.
Уже завтра.
Tomorrow's the day.
Ага.
Yup.
Нервуєшся?
Are you nervous?
А ти?
Are you, Sakura?
Серце калатає.
My heart is pounding.
Дивно, але в мене теж.
I wonder if I am...
Я так прагнула по-справжньому виступити.
I've been so eager to have our debut.
І ось вже завтра.
So thinking that it's tomorrow feels strange.
Не можу заспокоїтись.
I can't stay calm.
Після дебюту нас зареєструють у "Венеру".
When we make our debut,
we enter the Venus Program, right?
І тоді ми будемо суперницями.
Then we'll become rivals.
А?
What?
Найкращою групою може бути лише одна.
There's only one spot at the top.
Вдосконалюючись,
As we advance higher,
зрештою, колись ми заспіваємо на одній сцені.
we'll eventually sing on the same stage.
Коли прийде час,
When that time comes,
я не програю!
I won't lose!
Котоно...
Kotono...
Пробач.
Oh, sorry.
Я піду всередину.
I'm going back inside.
Котоно!
Kotono!
Я теж постараюсь,
I'll do my best, too.
щоб ми виступили на одній сцені.
For us to stand on the same stage.
І я не програю.
I won't lose, either.
Мг.
Yeah.
Суперницями, та?
Rivals, huh?
Гордість зірок.
Idoly Pride.
SPECIAL STAGE
Згадую день свого дебюту.
It takes me back to the day I made my debut.
SPECIAL STAGE
І це був єдиний день,
коли ти справді нервувала.
That was the only day you were
ever obviously nervous.
Та про що ти?
What? I was not.
Я ж геній, пам'ятаєш?
I'm a genius, remember?
Пам'ятаю, як ти...
You were.
одягла костюм неправильно,
You put on your costume wrong,
і ходила потім перед дзеркалом туди-сюди.
and paced back and forth
in front of the mirror.
А в останню мить сказала,
що не будеш виступати.
And to top it all off, you said you didn't
want to perform at the last minute.
Що, справді?
Did I really say that?
Ти забудькувата, коли тобі це вигідно.
You forget things
when it's convenient for you.
Та зовсім ні.
That's not true.
Це ти все перекрутив.
You're remembering things wrong.
Впевнена?
Are you sure?
Хоча це не важливо.
Well, it doesn't matter either way.
І то правда!
That's right!
Але...
But...
Я досі чітко пам'ятаю
кожний твій момент на сцені.
I still clearly remember the very
moment you stood on stage.
Як кожний день я бігав довкола,
готував усе, допомагав з уроками...
I ran around every day to get things
ready and help with lessons...
Ми разом придумували нові ідеї.
We thought of different ideas together.
І навіть сварились деколи.
We even fought at times, too.
Але в одну мить всі переживання розвіялись.
But the stress blew away all at once.
Хотів би знову зловити такий момент.
I want to witness that same moment again.
Напевне тому я й продовжую працювати тут.
That may be why I still continue to do this job.
Уже майже.
It's almost time.
Все добре.
It's okay.
Я точно впораюсь.
I'm sure it'll go great.
Наш вихід!
Here we go!
Сані Піс!
Sunny Peace!
Це відчуття в наших серцях
This feeling in our hearts
Всі разом
Together
Усі ми разом засяємо
Let's shine
Яскраво!
Brightly!
Мала б я до стежки, що в дім веде (звикнути уже)
I should be used to this path home (the usual town)
Але дивно, сьогодні немов вона яскравішою є{яскравішою стала
Але дивно, сьогодні немов вона яскравішою є
It's strange, it looks brighter today
Ніколи не забуду сліз з того дня
I won't forget the tears from that day
Обіцянка моя
That's a promise
Нетерплячість, мрії, захоплення
Impatience, dreams and excitement
Не хочу жалкувати про щось я
I don't want to regret anything
Та якщо колись загублюсь
If I do ever get lost
Найважливіше тут
The important things
Биття мого серця підскаже мені
The beating of my heart lets me know
Ці відчуття всередині, в душі
These feelings in my heart
Чи зможу зустріть
If I can face them
Я можу
I can
Зміцнити себе
Establish myself
І стати
Become
Навіть
Even
Сильніше
Stronger
Ці відчуття в наших серцях
This feeling in our hearts
Всі разом
Together
Усі ми разом засяємо
Let's shine
Яскраво!
Brightly!
Хочу освітити тебе яскраво!
I want to illuminate you brightly!
Sunny P! Sunny P!
Зараз ти тримай мене міцно.
Hold me tight right now
Що ж робить?
What should I do?
Серцебиття не припиняється
The beating doesn't stop
П'ять мирних знаків складемо, разом
Five peace signs together
Стануть зіркою
Become a star
Я хочу сяяти завжди
I want to shine all the time
Зробімо це.
Let's do this.
Мун Темпест!
Moon Tempest!
Самотня квітка цвіте вночі
A single flower blooms at night
Виду вона прекрасного й дорогоцінного
A precious and beautiful sight
І чому я сльози проливаю?
Why am I shedding tears?
Все, що переді мною не помічаю
Everything is out of focus in front of me
Жадібно повітря вдихала
I breathed hard
Уперед себе гляділа
I looked straight ahead
Але досі трошки я тремчу
But I was still trembling a little
В справжній темряві я
In the true darkness
Бачити геть нічого не могла
I couldn't see anything
Та дізналась що означає "сяяти"
But I found out what it means "to shine"
Місяця сяйво упаде на сяйво твоє
The moonlight shines on your light
Вперше відчуваю - це бажання справжнє
The first time I felt this true wish
Яскраве, щастя несе
It's so bright and brings happiness
Починає змінюватись усе
Everything starts to change
Підйоми і падіння струшують ту пітьму
The waxing and waning shakes the darkness in my heart
Вагатись більш не буду - з радістю прийму
I'll accept it and won't hesitate anymore
Буду робити скільки захочу я у цю мить
I'll do as much as I want to in this moment
Усе таке непевне
It's so uncertain
Можу впасти будь-коли
I could crumble at any moment
Але ти освітиш мене
But you illuminate me
Тому сяяти можу я
So I'm able to shine
Усім привіт!
Hello, everyone!
Ми, Сані Піс!
We're Sunny Peace!
І ми, Мун Темпест.
We're Moon Tempest.
Сьогодні провели наш
перший концерт разом!
We made our joint debut today!
Ми новачки, тому ще не дуже досвідченні,
We're newcomers so we're inexperienced,
але будемо наполегливо працювати,
but we will all work hard,
і мотивувати одна одну вдосконалюватись.
and motivate each other to continue to grow.
Також, як справжні айдоли,
ми прагнемо до вершини.
And, we'll work hard to aim
for the top as idols.
Удачі!
Good luck!
Буду вболівати за вас!
I'll be rooting for you!
Дуже вам дякую!
Th-Thank you very much!
Нарумія Сузу тут!
Suzu Narumiya here!
Мною пишається Хошімі.
Я - Нарумія Сузу,
I, Suzu Narumiya of Hoshimi City's
prided Hoshimi Production,
Сподіваюсь на вашу підтримку!
look forward to your support!
Сузу, але ж це не вибори.
Suzu, this isn't an election, you know?
Може зробити моє фірмове привітання?
Should I do my usual greeting, too?
Не варто...
I suggest you don't...
Сані Піс і Мунест!
Sunny P and Moonest!
Підтримуйте обох!
Support them both!
Послухай Мей.
Hey... Mei!
Агов, Рей!
GO REI!
Rei!
Ми за тебе!
We're rooting for you!
Мої колеги.
They're from my job!
Та годі тобі, помахай їм.
Come on Rei, wave back to them.
І ти теж, Шідзуку.
Come on, Shizuku. You, too.
Я буду старатись.
I'll do... my best!
Дякуємо вам усім!
Thank you very much!
Дякую!
Thank you!
Зараз...
Right now...
Їх світло ще непримітне,
Their light is still small.
Але Котоно та інші точно...
But Kotono and everyone will surely...
Дякуємо вам усім!
Thank you very much!
For a Precious Stage
kirameki sagashite
fumidasu ippo wa kiseki ja nai
tomadoi mo mayoi mo mada kakaeta mama
sore mo ii ne warau kimi ni sukoshi sunetari shite
itsunomanika itsumo no jibun ni naru
fushigi da keredo
kimi dake
kirameki no naka e
hizashi no atataka sa tsutsumarete
kagayaki no naka e
tsuki yo ni mo rinto sake
mabushisugiru kurai hoshi yo kagayake Shinin' Star